Guide to the Dick Thornburgh Papers, 1932- AIS.1998.30.17
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Ongoing Career, 1993; XVII.
  - Events, 4.
    - New Material Added, August 2018
      - American Bar Association 2009 Annual Meeting: Speaker topic- Role of the Attorney General vs. President, July 31, 2009 (Box 1067, Folder 10)
      - Meeting with Stacy Taylor (with David Case), August 5, 2009 (Box 1067, Folder 11)
      - PA Cable Network…Interview with" PCN Profiles", August 13, 2009 (Box 1067, Folder 12)
      - Sonia Sotomayor Swearing In at Supreme Court, September 8, 2009 (Box 1067, Folder 13)
      - Presentation of official portrait of Michael Mukasey, 81st Attorney General, September 10, 2009 (Box 1067, Folder 14)
      - WLF Annual Supreme Court Preview/ Media Briefing, September 15, 2009 (Box 1067, Folder 15)
      - Council on Foreign Relations Program: "Previewing Pittsburgh: The G20 and the Global Economy", September 18, 2009 (Box 1067, Folder 16)
      - Meeting with Diane Niemann & Suzan Onel, September 22, 2009 (Box 1067, Folder 17)
      - Reception and Luncheon Lecture by His Excellency Jose Manuel Barroso, President of European Commission European Union, University of Pittsburgh, September 24, 2009 (Box 1067, Folder 18)
      - Visit by His Excellency Dmitry A. Medvedev, President of Russian Federation, to University of Pittsburgh, September 24, 2009 (Box 1067, Folder 19)
      - Video text for Government Solutions Group at firm retreat, October 5, 2009 (Box 1067, Folder 20)
      - Rule of Law Forum, CSIS (Center for Strategic & International Studies), October 5, 2009 (Box 1067, Folder 21)
      - CMU Heinz College Class in DC: Focuses on public policy issues beginning with economic crisis, Three Mile Island, October 9, 2009 (Box 1067, Folder 22)
      - K&L Partners Retreat, Phoenix, AZ: "Elevating Client Service Through FIRM INTEGRATION", October 15-18, 2009 (Box 1067, Folder 23)
      - Interview in NYC with The Documentary Group re: Bill of Rights, October 23, 2009 (Box 1067, Folder 24)
      - Political "round table" Luncheon hosted by Chris Gleason & Jim Roddey, October 28, 2009 (Box 1067, Folder 25)
      - "Trip to Syracuse University"- prepared for Governor by Bill Snyder, November 4-6, 2009 (Box 1067, Folder 26)
      - Presentation notes of Governor at Syracuse, November 4-6, 2009 (Box 1067, Folder 27)
      - References with Governor's underlining, Part 1 of 2, November 4-6, 2009 (Box 1067, Folder 28)
      - References with Governor's underlining, Part 2of 2, November 4-6, 2009 (Box 1067, Folder 29)
      - CSIS Hills Program on Governance, November 23, 2009 (Box 1067, Folder 30)
      - Government Enforcement Practice Group Meeting, November 24, 2009 (Box 1067, Folder 31)
      - WLF Honest Services Media Briefing, December 2, 2009 (Box 1067, Folder 32)
      - Oral History Interview re City of Harrisburg, PA for 150th Anniversary of Incorporation, December 3, 2009 (Box 1067, Folder 33)
      - Pennsylvania Society Annual Dinner, December 12, 2009 (Box 1067, Folder 34)
      - Germantown Friends School Class talk, December 14, 2009 (Box 1067, Folder 35)
      - Urban Institute Breakfast and Discussion "conversation on education's next crucible", December 15, 2009 (Box 1067, Folder 36)
      - Government Solutions Group Meeting, December 18, 2009 (Box 1067, Folder 37)
      - Conference Call re: Austin TX Panel Program 1/14-15, January 6, 2010 (Box 1067, Folder 38)
      - Ginny's 70th birthday celebration, Cosmos Club, January 8, 2010 (Box 1067, Folder 39)
      - James Ford Bell Trust Reception in Honor of Unveiling of the "Impossible Black Tulip" 1602 massive map of world, January 12, 2010 (Box 1067, Folder 40)
      - Texas Public Policy Foundation Overcriminalization Panel Discussion on "Over-Criminalization of Business: More Laws, Less Freedom"; University of Texas, Austin, TX, January 14, 2010 (Box 1067, Folder 41)
      - PCN-TV Interview: Thornburgh's perspective on 2020 Elections, January 20, 2010 (Box 1067, Folder 42)
      - Meeting with Mark Ruge and Mayor Lippert (of Dallas), January 22, 2010 (Box 1067, Folder 43)
      - Roundtable with Reporter from Washingtonian Magazine, January 27, 2010 (Box 1067, Folder 44)
      - Lunch with Russians Verkhovsky and Pavlov, re: xenophobia in Russia, February 5, 2010 (Box 1067, Folder 45)
      - Grand Reopening of Civil War Room at Carnegie Free Library & Music Hall, Carnegie, PA; Reopening of Captain Thomas Espy Post No. 153 of Grand Army of the Republic, February 14, 2010 (Box 1067, Folder 46)
      - NACD Three Rivers Chapter: "Growing Pressures on Board Decision Making- When Public Debate Impacts the Board Room; Thornburgh Keynote Address; Pittsburgh, February 16, 2010 (Box 1067, Folder 47)
      - Washington Legal Foundation "High Court Halftime: The October 2009 Term at Midpoint, February 18, 2010 (Box 1067, Folder 48)
      - K&L Gates Firmwide Partners' Meeting, February 18, 2010 (Box 1067, Folder 49)
      - Meeting with Professor Alan Rosenthal re: Book writing on "How Governors Succeed", February 19, 2010 (Box 1067, Folder 50)
      - 2010 National Governors Association Former Governors Breakfast and Business Session, February 20-22, 2010 (Box 1067, Folder 51)
      - Telephone Interview, WHP-580; promoting upcoming speech at The State Museum on February 24, February 22, 2010 (Box 1067, Folder 52)
      - Video conference with Karen Hewitt, US Attorney for Southern District of California, February 22, 2010 (Box 1067, Folder 53)
      - Lunch with Young Woo Kang, Ginny, and Mrs. Kang, February 23, 2010 (Box 1067, Folder 54)
      - PA Bookstore Speakers Program & Book Signing, February 24, 2010 (Box 1067, Folder 55)
      - Interviews with Professor Bruce Ledewitz re: Oral History of 1967-68 PA Constitutional Convention (in DC), February 24-5, 2010 (Box 1067, Folder 56)
      - Lunch with Congressman Tim Murphy, March 10, 2010 (Box 1067, Folder 57)
      - AAPD Leadership Awards Gala, March 10, 2010 (Box 1067, Folder 58)
      - Lunch with Robin Ross, Metropolitan Club, March 11, 2010 (Box 1067, Folder 59)
      - Meeting with Dan Ritter, partner in Public Policy group re public policy emerging technology/science & philanthropic/non-profit sub-practice groups, March 15, 2010 (Box 1067, Folder 60)
      - "Kodak opportunity " meeting re: law firm, March 16, 2010 (Box 1067, Folder 61)
      - WLF Media Nosh on Overcriminalization: "Free Enterprise & Criminal Law", March 17, 2010 (Box 1067, Folder 62)
      - Speak at NACD Program in Portland Oregon; Invitation to speak "The Government is Watching: Changes in the Political Landscape and Implications for Business Governance", March 31, 2010 (Box 1067, Folder 63)
      - Telephone Interview; Brian Abzanka (CTV Pittsburgh)" Business Coalition for Homeland Security", April 8, 2010 (Box 1067, Folder 64)
      - Interview with Jeff Sewald of Pittsburgh Quarterly "What Do I Know", April 10, 2010 (Box 1067, Folder 65)
      - Interview with Andrew Stockey (WTAE) Pittsburgh Regional Business Coalition for Homeland Security, April 12, 2010 (Box 1067, Folder 66)
      - Pittsburgh Regional Business Coalition for Homeland Security Spring Meeting; Speech "Strategic Decision-Making in a Volatile Environment: Reflections on Three Mile Island", April 12, 2010 (Box 1067, Folder 67)
      - Meeting with Curt Weldon, member of Congress 1987-2007, April 14, 2010 (Box 1067, Folder 68)
      - 2010 Pennsylvania Leadership Conference Luncheon; Speech, April 17, 2010 (Box 1067, Folder 69)
      - FMI 2010 Legal Conference; Speech "Corporate Social Responsibility", April 18, 2010 (Box 1067, Folder 70)
      - Meeting with Fred Einbinder of Alstom Company issues, April 20, 2010 (Box 1067, Folder 71)
      - Federalists Presentation at Duquesne Law School, April 29, 2010 (Box 1067, Folder 72)
      - Documenting Leadership: A Symposium on Public Executive Records in the 21st Century; Albany Law School; Speech: "The Legacy of an Executive: A Governor's Perspective", May 20-21, 2010 (Box 1067, Folder 73)
      - Meeting with Mohit Saraf (with Jonathan Blank, et al.)Partner in Luthra & Luthra, June 3, 2010 (Box 1068, Folder 1)
      - Meeting with Carol Bruce, prospective litigator with the firm, June 4, 2010 (Box 1068, Folder 2)
      - Videotaped Interview for KLA-Tencor Corp: Merit Selection News Conference: Background Paper on "Growing Pressures on Board Decision Making: When Public Debate Impacts the Board Room" (March 2, 1010), June 18, 2010 (Box 1068, Folder 3)
      - Transparency International- USA: Policy Committee Meeting re: Corruption Issues, June 21, 2010 (Box 1068, Folder 4)
      - National Public Radio Interview with Nina Totenberg re: "honest services" statute, June 21, 2010 (Box 1068, Folder 5)
      - Luncheon for Tom Corbett candidate for Governor, June 22, 2010 (Box 1068, Folder 6)
      - Cathedral of Learning Society Induction Dinner, June 27 2010 (Box 1068, Folder 7)
      - Rosslyn Farms Community Reunion, July 3, 2010 (Box 1068, Folder 8)
      - Meeting, re: Hoover's report re: Braskem S.A., July 12, 2010 (Box 1068, Folder 9)
      - Photo shoot fo accompany Thornburgh article: "What do I Know Fall 2010", July 16, 2010 (Box 1068, Folder 10)
      - Dinner Honoring Marriage of Paul & Anke Volcker, July 18, 2010 (Box 1068, Folder 11)
      - Dinner with Manny & Marilyn Rouvelas, July 19, 2010 (Box 1068, Folder 12)
      - Visit to St. Vincent's Fred Rogers Center, July 16, 2010 (Box 1068, Folder 13)
      - Surprise 80th Birthday for Chuck Queenan, July 20, 2010 (Box 1068, Folder 14)
      - K&L Gates Firmwide Partners' Meeting, July 22, 2010 (Box 1068, Folder 15)
      - Testimony on Occasion of 20th Anniversary of Signing of Americans with Disabilities Act before US House of Representatives Committee on the Judiciary, July 22, 2010 (Box 1068, Folder 16)
      - White House Ceremony Commemorating 20th Anniversary of ADA, July 26, 2010 (Box 1068, Folder 17)
      - Dinner with Talmage Boston & Tom & Laura Leppert (Tom Mayor of Dallas), July 30, 2010 (Box 1068, Folder 18)
      - Taped Interview for Tribute to Jack Lawn, September 8, 2010 (Box 1068, Folder 19)
      - Guest Speaker (Paul Critchlow) for Bob Wilburn's Policy Analysis Capstone Class at Carnegie Mellon University, September 3, 2010 (Box 1068, Folder 20)
      - Gettysburg College Eisenhower Institute: Keynote Speaker at Constitution Day The Americans with Disabilities Act: Twenty Years Later", September 14, 2010 (Box 1068, Folder 21)
      - SSTI 14th Annual Conference Session: Technology-based Economic Development in Transition: A View from the Governors, September 15, 2010 (Box 1068, Folder 22)
      - WLF Media Briefing: October 2010 Supreme Court Term; Thornburgh Moderator, September 16, 2010 (Box 1068, Folder 23)
      - PBI/CLE Program on Constitutional Convention in Philadelphia, September 21, 2010 (Box 1068, Folder 24)
      - Espresso Book Machine (EBM) Reception, Main Reading Room, Hillman Library, September 27, 2010 (Box 1068, Folder 25)
      - Evening honoring "Jack" Lawn, recipient of 2010 DEA Educational Foundation Lifetime Achievement Award, September 30, 2010 (Box 1068, Folder 26)
      - Heritage Foundation "Preserve the Constitution" Series; Speech "Overcriminalization: Sacrificing The Rule of Law in Pursuit of Justice", October 6, 2010 (Box 1068, Folder 27)
      - National Academy o Public Administration. Meeting with Jenna Dorn and Lena Trudeau re NAPA (see letter), October 12, 2010 (Box 1068, Folder 28)
      - Celebration of 50th Anniversary of 1960 World Series Championship, October 13, 2010 (Box 1068, Folder 29)
      - 2010 Partners Meeting - Marriott Desert Ridge, Phoenix, October 14-17, 2010 (Box 1068, Folder 30)
      - Meeting with Jeff Brodsky, Graduate School Oral History Interview, October 19, 2010 (Box 1068, Folder 31)
      - AAPD/Launch Breakfast for Disability Mentoring Day, October 20, 2010 (Box 1068, Folder 32)
      - WLF Media Briefing: The States v. "ObamaCare"; Thornburgh Moderator, October 21, 2010 (Box 1068, Folder 33)
      - Presentation to Japan Commerce Association: "Best Practices in Crisis & Risk Management in Today's Political Environment", October 26, 2010 (Box 1068, Folder 34)
      - Dick Thornburgh Forum for Law & Public Policy Advisory Committee Meeting, November 15, 2010 (Box 1068, Folder 35)
      - Professional Development K&L Luncheon Program re. Congressional Procedures: House v. Senate, May 6, 2011 (Box 1068, Folder 36)
      - Meeting re: BUCERIUS LAW School in US, May 10, 2011 (Box 1068, Folder 37)
      - Twelfth Gerd Bucerius Lecture "Opportunities and Challenges in the 21st Century: The Future of Europe and the Transatlantic Partnership", May 10, 2011 (Box 1068, Folder 38)
      - Firmwide Partners Meeting, May 19, 2011 (Box 1068, Folder 39)
      - Meeting with Ron Gainer re: Overcriminalization, May 20, 2011 (Box 1068, Folder 40)
      - Visit to Children's Institute, Pittsburgh, May 20, 2011 (Box 1068, Folder 41)
      - Lunch with Barol Bruce Elder, Special Counsel, Report of Preliminary Inquiry into matter of Senator John E. Ensign, May 23, 2011 (Box 1068, Folder 42)
      - Meeting with Dr. Kang & Korean Delegation, May 26, 2011 (Box 1068, Folder 43)
      - Texas Supreme Court Historical Society Annual Banquet Austin; Speech: "Homeland Security, Civil Liberties and the Rule of Law", June 3, 2011 (Box 1068, Folder 44)
      - Keynote Speaker at Commonwealth Court Historical Society Annual Meeting, Harrisburg; Speech "Failures: An Unfinished Agenda", June 7, 2011 (Box 1068, Folder 45)
      - Lunch with Summer Associates, June 12, 2011 (Box 1068, Folder 46)
      - Capital Area Food Bank Tour with Ginny & Mark Ruge, June 20, 2011 (Box 1068, Folder 47)
      - Retirement Reception for John Wodatch, Great Hall Main Justice, June 20, 2011 (Box 1068, Folder 48)
      - Speaker at Pitt Inaugural Alumni Lecture Series "Lying or Complying? A Conversation on Ethics and Accountability", June 23, 2011 (Box 1068, Folder 49)
      - Moderator WLF 2010 Supreme Court Wrap-up Program, June 28, 2011 (Box 1068, Folder 50)
      - Conference Call with J. Heumann, K. Guernsey, S. DeCosse, J. Wodatch & R. Frohboese re: Disability Treaty, June 28, 2011 (Box 1068, Folder 51)
      - CLE/Professional Development Program- FCPA-UK Bribery Act, July 11, 2011 (Box 1068, Folder 52)
      - Professional Development Program- How to Determine Whether Information Is Material For Purposes of Securities Law Disclosure Requirements, July 19, 2011 (Box 1068, Folder 53)
      - Meeting with Ginny & Erin Morriarty Harrelson Re: Workforce Program, August 3, 2011 (Box 1068, Folder 54)
      - Flight 93 Memorial, Visit, August 26, 2011 (Box 1068, Folder 55)
      - Boeing-Argon Deal Completed; Conference call, September 2, 2011 (Box 1068, Folder 56)
      - CMU/DC Campus Class with Bob Wilburn re: State/Federal Crisis Management, September 8, 2011 (Box 1068, Folder 57)
      - Conference Call with Paul Critchlow & Rachel Hillerman re: Josh Mandel, Candidate US Senate, September 9, 2011 (Box 1068, Folder 58)
      - Speak at Dedication of Monument to Pentagon 9-11 Victims, National Memorial Park, Falls Church, September 11, 2011 (Box 1068, Folder 59)
      - American University/Washington College of Law Directors Dinner Honoring DRI Board Members, September 12, 2011 (Box 1068, Folder 60)
      - Washington Legal Foundation "Experts to Preview" October 2011 Supreme Court Term, September 14, 2011 (Box 1068, Folder 61)
      - Urban Institute Dinner re: "The State of Our Cities", September 20, 2011 (Box 1068, Folder 62)
      - Telephone Interview with Matthew D'Ippolito re: PLCB privatization, September 23, 2011 (Box 1068, Folder 63)
      - Capital Area Food Bank Breakfast; Bountiful Harvest Fundraising Breakfast, September 27, 2011 (Box 1068, Folder 64)
      - CSIS (Center for Strategic & International Studies) Book Presentation "Capitalism at RISK" by Joseph L. Bower, September 28, 2011 (Box 1068, Folder 65)
      - Reception for Nancy Boswell, President and CEO of Transparency International-USA, September 27, 2011 (Box 1068, Folder 66)
      - Matthew D'Ippolito call re PLCB Privatization (Follow-up), October 3, 2011 (Box 1068, Folder 67)
      - Telephone call with Charlie Thompson with Patriot News re: LCB, October 5, 2011 (Box 1068, Folder 68)
      - ALEC Conference call re: Over-criminalization, October 17, 2011 (Box 1068, Folder 69)
      - WINA Radio Interview with Jane Foy re: UVA Speech, October 18, 2011 (Box 1068, Folder 70)
      - Telephone Interview with Brian Bolduc of National Journal re: Justice Thomas 20 years on Court, October 18, 2011 (Box 1068, Folder 71)
      - Speak at UVA Center for Politics; Speech "Politics and Public Policy: How Do We Stand?", October 18, 2011 (Box 1068, Folder 72)
      - Telephone Call with Samuel Kleiner re: Gulf War & War Powers, October 19, 2011 (Box 1068, Folder 73)
      - Reception with Slad Gorton & Introducing the Slade Gorton International Policy Center, October 19, 2011 (Box 1068, Folder 74)
      - Telephone Call with Ron Gainer re: "Would-Be-Reformers", October 20,2011 (Box 1068, Folder 75)
      - World Bank Sanctions Procedures, Correspondence from Peter Korak, Managing Director, October 20, 2011 (Box 1068, Folder 76)
      - Conference call re: Kissinger Program 10/26, October 21, 2011 (Box 1068, Folder 77)
      - Pgh Middle East Institute Annual Conference Conversation with Dr. Henry Kissinger, October 26, 2011 (Box 1068, Folder 78)
      - PBS Independent Lens Series "Lives Worth Living", October 27, 2011 (Box 1068, Folder 79)
      - K&L Partners Retreat: Phoenix Arizona, October 27-30, 2011 (Box 1068, Folder 80)
      - Governor Thornburgh's "Skype Session" with Dean Delaney Students at Pitt, College of Business Administration, November 2, 2011 (Box 1069, Folder 1)
      - Edna Silberman Humanitarian Service Award to Dick and Ginny Thornburgh, November 3, 2011 (Box 1069, Folder 2)
      - Professional Development: Ethics: Globalization and the Changing Roles of In-house and Outside Counsel, November 4, 2011 (Box 1069, Folder 3)
      - Washington Legal Foundation, Advisory Board meeting hosted by White & Case, November 9, 2011 (Box 1069, Folder 4)
      - Guest Speaker E&Y Corporate Round Table Dinner, November 9, 2011 (Box 1069, Folder 5)
      - Sustainable Funding for Our Courts Luncheon Program, Dickinson School of Law, November 10, 2011 (Box 1069, Folder 6)
      - D-Day Reunion- Gettysburg Battlefield, November 11-13, 2011 (Box 1069, Folder 7)
      - Telephone call with Jeremy Pelofsky, Reuters DOJ Reporter re: Profile of Eric Holder, November 14, 2011 (Box 1069, Folder 8)
      - Urban Institute Board Dinner & Conversation with Jacob Lew, Director OMB, November 15, 2011 (Box 1069, Folder 9)
      - Meet and Greet Representative Pat Meehan, US Congreeman, PA, November 16, 2011 (Box 1069, Folder 10)
      - Celebrating K&L Gates Washington, D.C. Office 40th Anniversary, November 17, 2011 (Box 1069, Folder 11)
      - "Politics and Public Leadership" Fels Institute of Government, Philadelphia, November 30, 2011 (Box 1069, Folder 12)
      - Lunch with Bob Wilburn & Amit Mukherjee, World Bank, December 1, 2011 (Box 1069, Folder 13)
      - Pennsylvania Society Annual Dinner, December 10, 2011 (Box 1069, Folder 14)
      - House Judiciary Crime Subcommittee Hearing re. Criminal Code Reform; Testimony " H.R. 1823, "Criminal Code Modernization and Simplification Act of 2011", December 13, 2011 (Box 1069, Folder 15)
      - Firmwide Partners Meeting, December 14, 2011 (Box 1069, Folder 16)
      - Interview with National Public Radio: Decline in US Correctional Population, January 9, 2012 (Box 1069, Folder 17)
      - Reception for Young Woo Kang, January 9, 2012 (Box 1069, Folder 18)
      - K&L Professional Development CLE Program re: Preparing for Trial, January 17, 2012 (Box 1069, Folder 19)
      - Lunch with Lily Claffee & Rachel Brand (US Chamber) and Barry Hartman, January 19, 2012 (Box 1069, Folder 20)
      - Princeton Theological Seminary meeting Ft. Lauderdale, January 21-24, 2012 (Box 1069, Folder 21)
      - World Bank Sanctions Case No. 112, January 25, 2012 (Box 1069, Folder 22)
      - Meeting with Briana Green, Director of DC Area Outreach for Pittsburgh School of Law, January 31, 2012 (Box 1069, Folder 23)
      - Telephone call with Jan Murphy re: Elected Attorney General, February 1, 2012 (Box 1069, Folder 24)
      - Washington Legal Foundation Supreme Court Review: October 2011 Term at Midpoint, February 7, 2012 (Box 1069, Folder 25)
      - ABA Law Students, Georgetown University Law Center, lunch with "Experience Panel", February 18, 2012 (Box 1069, Folder 26)
      - Ukrainian Law Reformers, February 27, 2012 (Box 1069, Folder 27)
      - Meeting with Ukraine Delegation, Febrary 27, 2012 (Box 1069, Folder 28)
      - K&L Gates/University of Rochester Program: talking points "After the Crash: Thought on the Financial Crisis, The New Regulatory Regime, and Implications for Future Generations", March 1, 2012 (Box 1069, Folder 29)
      - Keystone Dinner and PA Whistlestop, Pittsburgh, sponsored by Republican Women of Ohio Valley Region, March 3, 2012 (Box 1069, Folder 30)
      - Memorial Service Dr. Young Woo Kang, March 4, 2012 (Box 1069, Folder 31)
      - Meet with David Freed (Candidate for PA AG) and Bob Branstetter (Campaign Manager), March 5, 2012 (Box 1069, Folder 32)
      - Interview for Walter Hickel Documentary re: Work on Exxon Valdez Settlement, March 13, 2012 (Box 1069, Folder 33)
      - Program re: Presentation of IPADE Drug Violence Survey, March 21, 2012 (Box 1069, Folder 34)
      - DOJ Presentation of Sherman Award to James F. Rill, April 10, 2012 (Box 1069, Folder 35)
      - Memorial Service for Dan Popeo, Washington Legal Foundation, April 16, 2012 (Box 1069, Folder 36)
      - ABA Section of Litigation/Attorney General Forum, Annual Conference in DC, April 19, 2012 (Box 1069, Folder 37)
      - Meeting with Jeffrey Sewald re: US Attorney firing scandal, workings of DOJ in general & Wecht trial, April 20, 2012 (Box 1069, Folder 38)
      - George Mason University Symposium re: Law & Economics of Crime & Punishment, April 20, 2012 (Box 1069, Folder 39)
      - Lunch with Ruth Wedgwood, John Hopkins University, April 23, 2012 (Box 1069, Folder 40)
      - University of Pittsburgh Commencement, April 29, 2012 (Box 1069, Folder 41)
      - DeMarco/Escudero Wedding, NYC, April 29, 2012 (Box 1069, Folder 42)
      - Teleconference re: Congressional Briefing on Overcriminalization, May 2, 2012 (Box 1069, Folder 43)
      - ACHIEVA Luncheon: Progress report on Innovation in Support of People with Disabilities, May 3, 2012 (Box 1069, Folder 44)
      - Yale Club of Pittsburgh, HYP Club, RLT Speaker, May 3, 2012 (Box 1069, Folder 45)
      - Conference call re: Elsie Hillman Program 5/17, May 4, 2012 (Box 1069, Folder 46)
      - Meet Sr. Litigation Counsel at Mourants, May 10, 2012 (Box 1069, Folder 47)
      - Congressional Briefing re: "Overcriminalization: Causes & Consequences", May 11, 2012 (Box 1069, Folder 48)
      - Award of Moynihan Prize to Paul Volcker & Installation of AAPSS Fellows, May 10, 2012 (Box 1069, Folder 49)
      - Harrisburg K&L Office 25th Birthday celebration, May 15, 2012 (Box 1069, Folder 50)
      - Rand/Roundtable Symposium on Corporate Culture & 20th Anniversary of Federal Sentencing Guidelines, May 16, 2012 (Box 1069, Folder 51)
      - Institute of Politics Release of Case Study on Elsie Hillman's work for GOP, May 17, 2012 (Box 1069, Folder 52)
      - Yale Classmates Reunion, Philadelphia, May 22-24, 2012 (Box 1069, Folder 53)
      - World Bank Group Sanctions Board Program "Up-Holding the Rule of Law in the Fight Against Corruption and Poverty", May 30, 2012 (Box 1069, Folder 54)